[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
I...
want you to bring Mr. Sarm back to us.
All I have to do is bring Mr. Sarm back
How hard can it be?
Sarm!
It's his first heartbreak,
so it hurts a fair bit.
Based on my twin sense,
I'm guessing that he's probably
taking some time off on some beach.
An island in the South...
Can you pick one for me?
Ko Pha-ngan.
But danger awaits.
You are fated to suffer
the same misfortune as your parents:
either by falling into the water
or by drowning.
You have been given
an impossible task, correct?
Do you think we're friends?
You're all bark and no bite.
Do you think prey
can escape the claws of this mighty tiger?
It seems like a lot of people
have been looking
for you lately.
Then who?
It's whatever, then.
I don't really care anyway.
I'll be going now.
Mr. Sib?!
Yes,
Mr. Sib.
You're still not awake?
I am now.
Is there a problem, Mr. Sib?
Any news?
I have found Mr. Sarm.
Where is he?
On Ko Pha-ngan.
I ran into him at a restaurant.
But at the moment,
I still do not know exactly
where he is staying.
I believe he is at a bungalow
near Haad Rin.
If not,
he is probably somewhere around that area.
Does this mean...
you're still on the island?
Precisely.
Good.
You've made good progress.
No wonder
you were able to track him down
in just a few days.
Well done.
Impressive. You live up to your name.
It's time to end this mission
by bringing the teeny-tiny tiger home.
[Your Third Series]
♫Still feeling lonely? Well, you've got me,♫
♫Keeping you busy every day♫
♫I might not be the one you wanted,♫
♫But give it time, you'll love me anyway♫
♫It's your heart, so it's your choice,♫
♫I won't ever stand in your way♫
♫But when they make you blue,♫
♫Can you please let me take care of you?♫
♫I'm here to love you as myself,
not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space
when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you,
no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart,
lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]
There he is.
I have found him.
Should I approach him directly,
or call the insurance company first
in case he gets feisty again?
Hello...
I mean no harm.
Mr. Sarm, do you...
have a moment?
I don't.
Occupied by loneliness.
If that is the case,
could you spare me
- five minutes?
- Not even a second.
And stop bugging me already.
Go away
before I lose any more of my patience.
Remember, Jam:
"No trouble.
Just bring him home."
With that being said,
"No trouble.
Just bring him home."
Just bring him home..."
Still sticking around?
I've got an idea.
If you don't leave right now,
I'll call a shaman
and seal your soul in a pot
so you'll disappear.
Or...
How about this pot of tom yum?
"Cause trouble..."
Cause trouble.
Cause trouble!
Don't bring him home!
No matter how many times
you tell me to leave,
I must tell you the truth, Mr. Sarm.
Right now,
it has been six months
since you disappeared.
This means that
you abandoned your work for six months.
Adisuan Farm is in trouble, you see.
Adisuan Farm?
And based on
what I have investigated so far,
there are still many things
that I have not been able to verify yet.
You should hurry back and deal with them.
With that being said,
please return home, Mr. Sarm.
Everyone needs you.
How could there be any problems?
I've already put everything in place.
There's no way anything could go wrong.
100 percent!
Understand,
Snoop?
Gosh...
You're tricking me with that?
Oh...
You know,
only an idiot
would fall for such a stupid trick.
An idiot!
If that is the case...
In case you have not noticed,
Mr. Sarmonkey,
your reputation
among the workers at your farm
is now in shambles.
Everyone is getting frustrated
by the countless projects
you started yourself
but never followed through on.
Is that so?
They have been abandoned.
You mean set adrift on a raft?
Help!
I have been set adrift on a raft!
Goodness me.
What if they got stranded on an island?
"I don't wanna be alone!"
"Aww, I'll drown
- Above all,
- or be stranded."
your family is deeply worried.
It would be best if you returned.
First and foremost,
my name is Sarm!
Not "Sarmonkey!"
My name...
isn't...
Sarmonkey.
I'm not a monkey!
The same goes for me.
My name is Jam,
not "Snoop" like you have been calling me.
I am not finished yet.
In two weeks,
Ms. Namnueng is getting married.
She wants you to be there
on her special day.
Oh, God!
Woo!
First, you used Adisuan Farm.
Now you're using Namnueng?
Let me tell you something.
She doesn't like it!
She doesn't care about love!
Someone like her will never get married.
And yet, Mr. Sib got married.
You weren't trying to scare me,
were you?
Why would I do such a thing?
I am not a ghost, like you called me.
How could I possibly scare you?
So...
shall we return home?
I'm not returning.
And stop forcing me already.
If you are not coming home today,
then when are you going to?
And what's it to you?
If you do, my mission will be complete.
Oh?
Mission complete.
Complete...
Please, Mr. Sarm.
Please come home with me.
If there is anything you need,
please let me...
Hey!
What the hell is this?!
Don't move!
I said don't move!
Or I'm going to stab him!
Do it!
There are security cameras
all over the beach.
Your names will be known across the island.
If you make it out alive today,
you won't be so lucky next time.
It's damn near impossible...
to track you down,
Mr. Sarm.
- Hey!
- Keep moving!
Why did you stop?!
- Hey!
Woo-hoo!
Come.
Ha-ha!
Let's go!
Mr. Sarm!
Mr. Sarm!!
Mr. Sarm...
- We'll flank them from there!
- Yes.
Quickly! Come on!
Hey! Where are they?!
Hey!
Hey...
From Pak Chong to Ko Pha-ngan,
were you being followed?
I was not.
Who do you think they are?
They were probably not your average thugs.
They were not after our belongings,
but you.
Moreover, they knew your name.
It seems like
they have been looking for you.
Apart from you, who Sib sent here...
did he send anyone else?
He only tasked me with bringing you home.
I know nothing apart from that.
Oh,
perhaps they're your enemies?
Did you step on someone's toes?
Think carefully.
I think you are the one
who should ask yourself
whether or not you have any enemies.
Seriously, you.
I was at peace,
and here you are causing me trouble.
I'm here to heal my heart,
and here I am
running away from thugs with you.
And where exactly are we going?
To the boat, obviously.
Just as they said.
Are you crazy?!
Why would you walk into their trap?
Never heard of it?
"The safest place
is often the most dangerous one."
What's wrong?
You're as pale as a boiled chicken.
Get up!
Quickly!
Come on!
Get up already.
Make it quick.
Come on!
Can we take it slow, please?
- Where are we going?
- What?!
Hey!
My backpack!
Would it kill you
to go without this backpack?
It surely would!
Hey!
Okay, okay.
Then remember this,
and take a good look
at who...
your hero is.
Take a good look
at who your hero is!
Yeah! I got it.
Why did you jump into the water?
You could have just taken it slow.
Normal is boring anyway.
Come on, Snoop!
Help me!
Hold on tight, okay?
Three, two, one!
Oh...
Let's get going already.
We need to hurry.
Why go overboard when we had to hurry?
You picked the worst time to go overboard.
Come on.
You are beyond help.
It is completely soaked!
Uncle.
Does the person you're waiting for
look like this?
Yes.
Make it quick.
I'm dying to eat my wife's cooking.
Okay.
Jam, hop on.
Come on.
Quickly.
But...
No more buts.
Hop on.
Ow...
You!
By the way,
where are you taking us, Uncle?
Where are the other two?
They're not coming.
You see,
this is why
I brought my partner on board instead.
Did you even ask me first?
Jam.
Or are you staying here?
Don't forget
what your mission was
when you came here.
So, Uncle?
The northern beaches of Ko Pha-ngan.
Come on.
Here.
Let's go.
We're almost there.
Over there.
Oh!
Uncle.
Do you even know how to drive?
Oh!
Hey! Jam!
Jam!
Stop the boat!
Uncle! Stop the boat!
Uncle!
Jam!
Jam!!
Little Jam...
Jam...
Jam.
Little Jam.
Little Jam...
Jam.
Little Jam.
Little Jam!
Jam.
It's me.
Don't worry.
You're still alive.
Mr. Sarm...
Don't say it like that.
You're making me nervous.
I was talking to Mr. Sarm this morning
before we were hunted down.
We then had to board a boat
with an inexperienced driver,
and it capsized.
Mr. Sarm carried me to shore.
I got upset with him
before passing out.
So how did I end up here?
- Ta-da!
- Whoa!
You almost died doing your job,
Snoop.
Don't tell me that
you've lost memory,
like they do in soap operas.
Wait! That means that you've forgotten
that I'm Prince Smith
from the House of
Smithru Smithra.
Wow.
And what about the boat driver?
Oh...
The lifeguards came to rescue him
the moment the boat capsized.
As for you,
I jumped into the water
and dove around looking for you...
Then I found you.
I found your backpack, too.
And where is it?
I left it on the fish-drying raft to dry out.
And what about you?
How are you feeling?
I am so hungry,
I am starting to feel dizzy.
If you're okay now,
we'll have some food later.
Oh.
Here.
Ta-da!
Your outfit.
I've got a new one for you.
What do you think?
Feeling touched yet?
Let me go get changed real quick.
Hey! Ta-da.
Let me lend you a hand.
[Ministry of Public Health]
[Emergency]
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to stay here
for a change of pace.
I've already filmed my MV there.
I used all the landmarks at that beach.
As for you,
it's best if you go home.
You've been getting into trouble
every day here.
You, too, should return home.
It is not yet time.
Let's go.
What about my wallet and phone?
Maybe they were lost at sea.
My phone's gone, too.
This means neither of us...
has any money on us.
Hm...
Only you do.
Not me.
The banknotes got soggy,
but while you were recovering,
I, myself,
went out and withdrew some cash.
And here.
I bought us some yogurt drinks.
I might as well have some.
Ta-da.
Ah! That's refreshing.
Come on, follow your man... Wait!
Can you walk properly?
Here to retrieve the backpack?
Oh.
Thank you.
My backpack.
Mm.
Can you see me clearly now?
Am I still as handsome as ever?
Did Sattawat
send you here
just to bring me home,
or to be my burden?
I could not see very well.
I never intended to be your burden either.
You didn't even say "thank you."
I will thank you all at once
by returning the favor with total devastation.
I will make sure
it is an experience to remember.
Whoa.
Stick to your word,
Snoop.
Come on, let's go.
Hey...
wait for me.
Mr. Sarm!
Mr. Sarm...
This way!
Mr. Sarm,
you eat like a competitive eater.
Just enjoy your crab fried rice
and leave my food alone.
Why so stingy?
Take that back.
I'm stingy?
I ordered you this big platter
of crab fried rice.
Eat up already.
Whoa.
You are eating three kilograms each
of shellfish and crab.
That is totally unfair.
Hey.
Be polite when talking to
your elders, alright?
If you keep being this full of yourself,
no one will share anything with you.
You are full of excuses.
You want some?
Try closing your eyes.
Closing my eyes?
Do it.
Close your eyes...
and just dream about
eating seafood.
Are you full now?
Gosh!
You have endless money,
yet you will not even spare me a few crabs?
I don't waste my time on petty chatter.
Can you
even spell
"generosity?"
Uh...
Mm...
Oh.
I don't.
You want some?
Ask nicely.
I would rather not.
I will remember how stingy you are.
I will make sure I never forget it.
Here.
Take it.
Mr. Sarm,
you are always
blowing hot and cold with me.
Just so you know,
once you regain your strength,
you'll go back to constantly shouting at me.
You know that?
You can't have that.
Hey, you...
Do not play with your food.
"Do not play with your food."
Play what?
Give it back.
Hey!
You know,
crabs have families, too.
This is a crab family with their baby.
You can't tear them apart.
Eat that instead.
They're a family. How dare you separate them?
Gosh.
No one can hurt you.
Don't worry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[Restaurant]
[Flora Aloha]
[Reception, 100 meters]
Give me your hand.
You're such a burden.
You were the one
who dragged me onto the boat.
Good evening.
Could I borrow the phone for a moment?
Uh...
We're really sorry.
There's a storm right now.
The phone signal and Internet are down.
They're expected to be back
in about three days.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Thank you.
Huh?
What?
What are you doing here?
You rented this resort for me, did you not?
What are you on about?
You...
You are staying here, too?
You think you have that much of a choice?
But...
Your room
is this way.
Knock, knock, knock.
Do it!
There are security cameras all over the beach.
Your names will be known across the island.
Mr. Sarm...
You want some?
You're pretty cute when you're quiet,
you spooky kitten.
Hey.
Hey, you.
- Mm.
- Oh...
Oh, my!
What is it?
Hey.
You're not going to take a shower?
Gosh, we've been to so many places today.
We've been out in the sea breeze,
the sun, and the rain all day.
What if you get sick and die?
If you die,
I'll let the stingrays have you.
I'm not worried about you or anything.
What are you doing in my bedroom anyway?
Hey, I've been sitting here
for over five minutes
just to see
if you've showered yet.
You didn't even care...
and you still refuse to take a shower.
With the A/C this cold,
what if you get sick and die?
You are the one who has to go.
This is my bedroom, after all.
Go take a shower already.
Here.
Huh?
I'll take you to the bathroom.
Come on. I'll take you to shower.
I'll shower after you, Jam.
You go first.
This is my bedroom.
Fine.
I guess I'll leave.
Mr. Sarm...
He cannot stop saying unpleasant things.
Hey, mister.
Do you think I'm high up in the tree?
I thought I could finally rest.
Then something came up again.
Huh.
You can't climb a tree, can you?
I can't, obviously.
But I'll tell you this:
I won't lose to anyone.
You call that high?
Watch this.
Ah!
Jam, come and look at this.
Mr. Sarm?
No need to scream;
I do daring things like this every day.
What on earth are you doing up there?
The kids challenged me.
It is true that they did,
but you did not have to act tough
and take the challenge.
Can you even spell "give in"?
Pull yourself together.
Quit rambling, will you?
Help me down first.
Cannot be bothered.
You got yourself up there,
so get yourself down.
Let's go.
Jam.
Ow...
Did it hurt that much?
Oh, these scratches?
Nothing at all.
Nowhere near my heart.
Ow.
I will be gentle, okay?
Let me know if it hurts.
Okay.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Jam!
Are you trying to murder me?!
You're still laughing?!
Ow...
Want me to patch you up?
Listen.
Do not do crazy stunts again.
Crazy stunts?
Ever since I met you,
you have been nothing but trouble.
What did I do?
When I first met you,
you were drunk and causing a scene.
After that,
you jumped into the water on your own.
Today,
you had a tree-climbing contest
with the kids.
And now you have gotten yourself hurt.
I still do not know
what you have been doing
for the past six months.
But from what I can tell,
you probably do not live
like normal people do, right?
You're good at guessing.
Can you tell me
what you have been doing?
I want to know
what kind of cool things
a cool guy like you likes to do.
Finally,
something nice to hear.
You did not go out, capsize a boat,
and end up floating
in the ocean at night, did you?
That helps put my mind at ease, though.
But it is dangerous.
At night, the land breeze blows out to sea.
You might vanish with the tide
before you know it.
It's normal to feel like
doing something daring, right?
Still feel like doing that now?
I do not think so.
Don't lay it on so thick.
I already feel guilty enough.
Oh, you.
24 hours on this island
feel like 24 years to me.
There's the mystery behind
why people are hunting Mr. Sarm,
why he refuses to go home,
and how to mend his heart.
Gosh...
I can't figure out any of them.
Hey.
Huh?
Come and have a meal with me.
You are inviting me?
Yeah.
Eating alone...
makes everything taste a bit bland.
Mm.
- Why did you flinch?
- Ow!
It hurts.
Why do you refuse to go back
to your bungalow to pack your things?
You left a lot of your things back there.
There's so much stuff.
It's such a hassle
to move it all.
Still, there are
so many of your things there.
If someone found out,
it could get you into trouble.
Are you worried about me or my stuff?
I am...
worried about my work.
Huh...
Worried about your work?
Have you been back in Thailand long?
I came back here when I was seven
and have been living here ever since.
Have you thought about...
when you'll leave for a place
where you'll find peace?
I will find peace after you kick the bucket.
Sharp tongue, aren't you?
How old are you?
23?
Why do you care?
Age is just a number.
Hey.
Where did Sib find you, anyway?
I mean...
how did you end up working with him?
If I answer your question,
you have to answer mine, too.
Wow...
You really know
how to drive a hard bargain.
But that's okay.
I'm always fair.
You ask, I ask.
You answer, I answer.
Why did you come to Ko Pha-ngan?
I was heartbroken.
My turn.
You were sent to find
a good-looking guy like me.
Isn't your partner jealous?
My partner understands that
I am here for work.
A fictional partner doesn't count.
So what?
My turn, then.
Now that you have abandoned your work,
who has taken the helm?
Thee, obviously.
I'm close to him.
I might even be closer to him
than I am to Sib.
Oh.
Like what Song said.
Mr. Thee...
Is he a relative of yours
around the same age as Mr. Sib?
You call him by his name?
Are you two close?
That is what Dr. Song wants me to call him.
I'm the same age as Song,
and I'm way older than you.
Why don't you call me the same way?
Why do you not
address me more politely, then?
My turn.
When are you returning home?
Probably not anytime soon.
Wanna sing a song?
Get a perfect 100,
and your food is on the house.
No, thank you.
What a shame.
Someone got a perfect score this afternoon,
so their bill was on us.
Where's the microphone?
You scared me.
I'm Four, and you're Mod.
Hey, wait...
What?
Please no.
I am embarrassed.
Oh, embarrassed about what?
There are so many people here.
That is what makes it
even more embarrassing!
Oh, don't feel that way.
Come on, let's go.
Sing a song!
We've found Mr. Sarm.
He's on the fishing village side
of the island
with Mr. Sattawat's assistant.
Let's do this.
Alright.
Leave the assistant be.
I want no trouble with him.
As for Sarm,
if disappearing is truly what he wants,
let us grant him his wish.
Understood.
[Mission: Hunt Down the Teeny-tiny Tiger]
My mission
is not yet complete.
Mr. Sarm still refuses to return home.
However, today,
I came to understand that
it is not his body
trying to escape,
but his heart seeking refuge.
Over the past 24 hours,
I have seen a man
who pretends to be tough,
fights against his own feelings,
loves to win,
and refuses to let anyone know
when he is in pain.
Maybe...
bringing him home
is not about bringing him back to the farm,
but about...
bringing him back to his old self.
And it seems like...
my mission has only just begun.
If you want to get over it,
the first step is accepting the truth.
Someday,
you will find someone you love
who loves you back.
We've been through so much together,
so how about we become friends?
Mr. Sarm!
Where are you, Mr. Sarm?
♫I'm here to love you as myself,
not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space
when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you,
no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart,
lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]